Let's make a lot of noise [cheering]
for Mr. Ian Bag. Ladies and gentlemen,
what's going on people that didn't have
anything else to do?
Poor women. Did he say you guys are
lesbians? Is that what he said?
[laughter]
I thought he said the front row was gay.
That's what I thought I heard. I like
that was hardcore. Just comes right out.
You homos
sitting at the fronting sex on sex
gentle.
Thanks girls. Thanks for wearing tube
tops.
I just seen them putting their tits back
in their tops. I [\h__\h] awesome.
They're doing one of these. They're
moving their jugs all around. I was like
[laughter]
turned me into a [\h__\h] 15-year-old
boy.
Except for I'm not hard cuz I'm in my
50s and it takes a while.
If I was 14, I would have been hard as a
rock. Wouldn't been able to do the show.
But I got about 17 18 minutes and then
all of a sudden it's just going to come
out of nowhere.
Thanks to those ladies lifting their
titties back into their shirts. All
right, girls. Your turn. Anyways,
[laughter]
your turn. Are you a biker gang? I feel
like you're a biker gang. Couple scooter
girls. Four scooter girls coming down to
the Ontario mall on youring Vespas
riding out from West Coina. Yum yum yum
yum yum
2 by two 4 deep coming out to the old
mall.
All right, good talk. [laughter]
I guess I'll go back to the girls
lifting their titties back in their
shirt. Oh, buddy, you missed it.
You picked the wrong time to take a
deuce, bud.
you were gone. They lifted their tits
back into their shirts. They were in
their pants. They took them right out of
their pants and put them back in their
shirts. They took them out from They
went They took them from being low to
high. It was crazy. Meanwhile, these
biker [\h__\h] have threatened me four
times. They're going to take their
Vespas and circle me after the showum.
You made a mistake, mother. Pecking on
us.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
Now we're all going to get carbon
monoxide poisoning from those motors.
Anyways, where were you, buddy?
>> Leaky.
>> What?
>> Oh, take did you say leaky? [laughter]
She talk to me like I was your mom.
Awesome. Where were you, Joseph?
Leaky, mommy. Leaky. [laughter]
Oh, I love this crowd. I thought you
guys were going to be dicks, but you
made me happy.
Turns out you're okay.
Oh my god, what a time for sports, huh?
Soccer and MMA at the same time.
>> Conor McGregor fought for almost a
minute 10.
>> He's back. He'sing not back.
Pulled a muscle walking like this. He's
[laughter]
too old. You can do that when you're in
your 20s, but when you're 37, you're Oh.
Oh.
Gets kicked in the head. Oh, I shouldn't
have done that. My hip. Oh, my head. Oh,
my hip. Oh my head. Oh, my hip.
Do you guys know about soccer? And girls
and girls, you play on a soccer team.
>> Did you girls come here to fight me?
Cuz I'm trying to be your friend right
now. And you just keep looking at me. We
don't know you. Don't try to talk to us.
[\h__\h] off, sir.
Ma'am, get off your phone or I'll punch
you in the tit.
>> I know where they are. You showed me
where they were earlier.
>> Who are you texting? Were you checking
the
>> Finding a drink?
>> You're finding a drink?
Oh my god. What are you looking for? Are
you ordering it from someplace else?
[laughter]
Get one of those. Those people got bad
vaginas.
They're ordering red drinks. They got
cranberry juice. They got the bad puss.
They went for a swim in a pond and it
got in her. She got bad jube jube in
hering.
[laughter]
>> Is that cranberry juice, ma'am? Or what
is it?
>> Tell us what it is. My friend's looking
for a drink, but she's reading. She's
reading the internet to find whating
drink she wants. Dear chat GTP, what
would I like to drink right now?
It says I want aing margarita with a
touch of lime.
Get all up. Are you new lesbians? What
are you drinking?
>> Old fashion.
>> Oldfashioned lesbians.
>> I don't know if you've ever heard about
oldfashioned lesbians. They don't wear
their seat belts and then they scissor
fight.
That's an oldfashioned lesbian right
there. I'm not wearing my seat belt and
then I'm going to put my lips on your
lips. [laughter]
Finger bangers. Are you finger bangers?
I'm a finger bangering way back. That's
my move right there. [laughter]
How many times you shower a week, ma'am?
Either one. Whoever wants to answer at
this point. [laughter]
>> Seven or eight.
>> Seven or eight. What? What? What takes
it up to eight. [laughter]
I think we'd all like to know what you
do on that one day. [laughter]
Seven or eight. Depends. If I seed my
friend David, [laughter]
I'm going to have to get the jizz off my
leg. So, a shower.
>> Sorry, ma'am. You do not seem to find me
funny at all. You're just looking at me.
Don't get jizz on girls legs. [laughter]
It belongs on their back. That's where
the tattoo.
>> How come you shower sometimes eight?
>> What's that?
>> Work two jobs.
>> You work two jobs and one you get clean
for. [laughter]
One day you shower for both jobs. The
other day is just one you get clean for.
But on the Sunday you work at
Chick-fil-A and you kill chickens.
That's the day they kill the chickens. A
lot of people think they're closed for
Jesus, but that's actually the day they
kill the chickens. Slaughter day. That's
what they kill.
Yeah, thanks for nodding. [laughter]
That's what you did for that joke. I see
your point.
>> [laughter]
>> They probably do have to kill a chicken
on some day, but I don't know if it's
Sunday they kill the chickens. What's
your favorite thing to get from
Chick-fil-A?
>> I don't eat a Chick-fil-A.
>> You don't eat a Chick-fil-A? Why not?
Cuz of the gays.
[laughter]
>> I don't eat.
>> Should I not talk to you? [laughter]
You seem very nervous and I don't want
You seem like you're going to throw up
if I have.
What do you eat at Chick-fil-A? No.
>> [laughter]
>> Please don't ask me questions. You
really should just check the internet to
see what I did before you accepted
[laughter] those seats. Cuz I've been
doing this a long time. You're like,
"How did you find me?" I look down.
You're in it. You're in it. All right.
Umpire. What? What do you
You're dressed like a [\h__\h] uh kids
softball umpire. You know that? Straight
from the games, right to the COMEDY
SHOW. YOU'RE OUT of here. And we are
too. We got [laughter] a big show we got
to go see. You go to Chick-fil-A. Can I
talk to you? Will you throw up?
[laughter]
Don't throw up. Can I talk to you? You
go to Chick-fil-A? No.
>> Where do you go? Where do you go?
>> In and out.
>> In and Out.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Seven or eight. [laughter]
>> Where do you work? Seven or eight.
>> Well, I work at a
>> Don't look at her. Look at me.
Don't check with her. She already knows
you. I don't know you. I'm talking to
you right now. I'm just talking to you.
I'm not trying to sleep with you. My
wife will not let me [\h__\h] other people.
>> She's kind of a [\h__\h] Anyways, let's
move on.
>> I work at a Jersey Mike.
>> She works at a Jersey Mike's. That's the
one they make her clean for.
>> No, after that one.
>> After that one. After that one. She's
got sandwich all over. She's got to go
home for a shower. I got to scrub up. I
got to go to my second job, which is at
>> a gym. A gym. Which one? 24-hour
fitness.
>> Powerhouse.
>> Powerhouse. Oh my god.
>> 24 hours.
>> It's what? Is it 24 hours? Just a bunch
of guys lifting the most weight ever.
>> Powerhouse.
>> Which one do you like better? Do you
like the Jersey mics or do you like the
the gym?
>> Well, I'll say
>> don't look at her. Don't look at her.
[laughter]
Has she kidnapped you? If you need help,
you will get you back to your family.
>> I don't know what's going on. I feel
like she's treating you very badly and
making you come to comedy shows when you
don't want to come [laughter] to Well, I
like working at Jersey Mike, but she
says I should like the powerhouse more.
[laughter]
>> She means you cuz I heard she's a
fingerbanger.
>> Oh my god. Well, I was going to say Jim
cuz I met her there.
>> You met her there? No. [laughter]
>> So, remember earlier when I said, "Are
you guys lesbian?" [laughter]
>> And you guys said no.
Well, that's the most gay answer I've
ever heard in my life.
Good luck, ma'am. She's going to try to
trick [laughter] you into something
later on. Can you spot me?
I'm doing squats.
>> [laughter]
>> Get underneath me and if I fall, I'm
hoping.
[laughter]
Do you do you wear the yoga pants at the
old gym? Do you get the old camel toe
moose knuckle going on?
Girls love to wear those pants. You can
see the You can see your lips.
[laughter]
It's tough. We tough to work out when
you're doing this.
[laughter]
Then you got that one machine where you
spread your puss
and then you make us look like we're the
[\h__\h] as you're as we're walking by
and you're spread eagle. Oh, hi. How are
you? You [\h__\h]
Whatever long lips McGee, you get
[\h__\h] [laughter]
You can see your whole snarch right
there.
Anyways, I don't know why I'm so mad
about that.
[laughter] It's cuz you yell at us. just
couldn't give us a wink, so you noted
that we're looking.
You're never going to have it.
[laughter]
That'd be better. But you met her at the
gym. Well, how did she come up? Hey, my
locker isn't working.
What she say at the gym? How'd she meet
you?
>> No clue.
>> Are you on drugs?
>> I'm worried about you. You seem young
and influenced.
>> How old are you?
>> I'm 24. 24. My god. New car smell.
[laughter]
Just fresh off the factory room for
show. How old are you?
>> Oh, 37.
>> 37. Let her live. Grandma.
That was a guy. 37y old guy and a 24
year old girl. Everybody be up in arms
because they're women. See? Well, we
shall overcome.
Give me a break. [laughter]
But at the same time, fantastic.
Young puss and old puss all in the same
car.
And grandma with her two hairs hanging
off her.
Sorry. Uncalled for. You probably have a
lovely vagina. Ma'am,
everybody like We'd all like to see it.
Order one, ma'am. Get her. Go on the
internet and find it.
What do you do? What What do you do?
Girl that met the other girl at the gym.
Yeah.
>> My stay at home mom.
>> You're a stay at home mom. [laughter]
>> She's She's got an only fans.
>> The kids are at school and mama's got
one leg up above the another by her ear
pretending she's a cat.
[laughter]
14.99. You can see this.
Good for you. How many kids you got?
Four. You look. Yeah. Somebody over
here. Holy.
[laughter]
Some guy just looked at his wife and
said, "Holy."
>> You can do that, too. [laughter]
>> Good for you. It's impressive. How old
are the kids?
>> Um, 8, seven, five, and three.
>> 8, seven, five, and three. Yes.
>> So, I'm going to say not the same
father.
>> Off.
>> You can't have that kind of weird
gapping and say, "Yeah, but this guy
just went away for two weeks and they
came back." Hold on here. This lady came
to Hey, I didn't say that. Yeah, but you
just drank a cranberry juice. Your puss
is no good.
>> Fantastic. Good for you. Don't let
anybody push you around. here. Great
mom. Even though it took me a long time
to figure out how old they were.
>> Eight, seven,
[laughter]
>> five, and three.
>> Oh, I love that. Get down. You've peed
too many times.
>> Is that the same guy? [laughter]
>> Prostate.
>> Bad prostate.
>> Did you just judge another man's
prostate?
How could you tell by the way he walked?
Oh, [laughter]
>> poorly. What's that?
>> Drink less.
>> Yeah.
>> That's not how a prostate works out
there. [laughter]
>> It helps me.
>> It helped you?
>> Yeah.
>> How old are you?
>> 40.
>> Yeah. Shut up. [laughter]
>> You have no idea about a Pratt prostate.
If you think you can just drink less,
ma'am, give him your chat. GTP.
Let him look at it. That guy isn't he
guy works at a at a goddamn Best Buy and
he's like
>> I'm gonna tell you guys how to fix your
prostate.
>> Shut the up.
>> That's why he's retired.
>> What's that?
>> He's retired.
>> 45.
>> Hold on everybody calm down.
>> 45 and he's retired. What the
>> Where did you retire from?
>> Look at me.
>> Investments.
>> What? Shh. [laughter]
>> What? Good investments.
>> Cocaine.
>> Investments. And
>> that's why your prostate hurts cuz you
smuggled it up your ass.
>> Mule just now told you how to keep less
water inside you. Drink less and shove
another condom up there.
>> For every beer you don't drink is
another 2 ounces of cocaine to get
across the border. [laughter]
>> Oh, buddy. You left, you picked the
wrong time to leave.
You left. That guy judged your prostate
and then this cocaine dealer came out of
nowhere
just like I'll tell you how to fix a
prostate. Little sniff sniff on your t
touch. Yeah. Yeah.
Meanwhile, the 24 years old,
>> I want a mommy. [laughter]
>> That guy just bragging about cocaine.
She said what?
>> I spoke up.
>> You spoke up.
>> You didn't brag about it.
>> My dad's still working.
>> What's that?
>> My dad still works.
>> Your dad still works.
>> Your your dad still works.
>> I know.
>> You're retired and your dad works.
>> You're an [\h__\h]
You get back to work and let your dad
sit down, you son of a [\h__\h] [cheering]
>> That's co.
Still talking like a typical cokehead.
[laughter]
Get off the blow and let your dad sleep
a little bit, you son of a [\h__\h]
>> What's that, man? His dad is still
>> His dad is still working.
>> Yes, he's still with us. We're good.
>> He's still with you.
>> Yeah, we're good. [laughter]
>> Ma'am, annunciate.
[laughter]
>> His dad is super blessed.
>> Super blessed.
>> Explain why the Explain what you're
talking about.
>> Holy.
>> Put that drink down. You make no sense
at all. [laughter]
His dad's still working. He's super
blessed. He could be dead by this age.
But he's still working. That's a
blessing in our books. Thank you, Jesus,
for making papa work.
That was Ricky Bobby, too. I just talked
to right there.
And my dad super blessed for having to
work at 85 years old. He wanted to
retire, but I made him work. Get back
out there, old man. Get out there.
Those potatoes ain't going to pick
themselves. Come on, [\h__\h] [laughter]
He's got good hips. We're blessed. We're
blessed with his hips.
His father has birthing hips.
Very interesting. All right, you guys.
Who wants to talk on this side?
[applause]
Couple with matching shirts. You guys
seem nice. Seem to have the same logo.
What's the logo on your shirts?
>> Gasoline Forever. Gasoline forever.
[laughter] Holy.
Sounds like you're very mad at electric
cars.
Gasoline forever, mother.
All right.
[laughter]
Are you really mad at electric cars?
>> What's that?
>> Are you really mad at electric cars?
[laughter]
Have you ever drove one?
>> Yes.
>> And and did it make you mad
>> cuz you just It just was just going
fast, but you couldn't hear it.
WHAT THE GOING ON? I PUSH HARDER, BUT
NOISES COMING OUT. It's You could hear
it with gas. Just sounds like farts.
Do you What kind of car do you own? What
kind of car?
>> Okay, pick one. [laughter]
>> What's that?
>> A Dodge Viper. A dodge fighter.
>> What kind of What kind of car do you
drive? Cocaine.
[laughter]
>> Easy escalator.
>> He has an easy escalator
>> cuz you can put drugs in the battery.
>> I got a frunk for the drugs.
>> What's that?
>> I have a frunk for the drugs.
>> He has a frunk. [laughter]
>> Oh, if you're trying to make your sound
cell sound straight, that did not work.
I have to go with gasoline on this one.
Don't ever say frunk again.
>> Well, just might as well just ask to
suck my dick after you said that. That
was
I got a frunk.
>> Put your [\h__\h] in my mouth.
>> Yeah.
For her.
>> That That place is for her.
>> For her.
>> Uhhuh. Yeah, man. She sucks [\h__\h]
>> I drive a Harley.
>> You drive a Harley?
>> I like it. Good for you. Gasoline.
Gasoline, baby.
>> Gasoline. Y.
>> Do you do motorbikes as well, sir?
>> What?
>> Do you do motorbikes as well?
>> Yes.
>> Y, brother.
>> Hey, brother.
>> I like it when motorbikers get along. I
don't like when gangs get all mad.
>> No, I know. Gangs are motor clubs.
>> Love you.
Just mumble.
>> Are you in a biker gang? No,
>> no, [laughter]
>> no. Club. [snorts]
>> No,
>> no. [laughter]
>> Maybe you guys should hang out and start
your own club.
Have your father do the taxes. He's
still working.
[laughter] He's very blessed. He'd love
to have another client.
You guys could start yourself. You could
call Gasoline Forever. Motorcycle Club.
Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum.
We could take your motorbikes, put them
on the back of the Escalade, drive them
someplace, and then drive them around.
Okay. And how did you meet your wife,
sir?
>> School.
>> A
>> Aost [laughter]
people are homeschooled.
That's why they made that noise cuz they
couldn't meet anybody at school. Their
brother was the only one in the class
who wants to. He's ugly.
>> What grade were you in?
>> High school.
>> 12th grade. It's fun, huh? What'd you
say to her?
>> Uh, let's get it on. [laughter]
Just started fighting right there.
Jiu-jitsu. Did you take her down in
jiu-jitsu? What did you do, [laughter]
ma'am? Do you remember when he said,
"Let's get it on?"
>> You don't. He didn't say that, did he?
He's like, "Hey, I was smiling my way
in the box."
And then came back and talked to you
another time.
I really really like you.
Got a lot of cars. You want to go for a
ride?
Gasoline forever.
[laughter] I love it. Seem like a nice
couple. A lot of kids. You guys got a
lot of kids?
>> Two.
>> Two. It's not a lot. This lady has got
four
five different guys. [laughter]
>> Cuz I'm Mexican.
>> What's that? What's
>> cuz I'm Mexican.
>> It's cuz you're Mexican. Is that what
you said?
>> No, I was going to say cuz it was a gang
bang.
It's completely different. But
[laughter] just out of the blue, you
blame the Mexicans for no apparent
reason.
Are you Mexican? [laughter]
Oh, thank God. After you said that, it's
[\h__\h] fair. I don't know if you know
where we are, but you just can't say
that.
[laughter]
I would say in 3/4 of this place could
be
[laughter]
Mexican.
I don't want to say it. [laughter] Is
there any Mexicans here? [cheering]
>> See how easy that was? How can the
government not find you people?
Like, it's so easy. I don't know why Ice
has to wear camouflage and pretend. Just
[laughter] get a bullhorn. Any Mexicans
here? All right, everybody get on. Let's
go. Come on. Let's go, everybody.
[laughter]
Are you Are you Mexican? Are you?
>> No.
>> No. What are you
>> from Ecuador?
>> You're from Ecuador?
>> Huh? [laughter]
Did not see that coming. Anybody else
see that coming? I do not know how to
respond to you. [laughter]
I'm going to take a lucky guess and say
that's near the equator.
Huh? Ecuador. What does that mean in
English? What does Ecuador mean in
English?
>> Equator.
[laughter]
>> Is that your husband behind you?
>> How'd you meet him?
>> We were introduced.
>> You were introduced. Oh no. Jeffrey
Epstein.
No, we were married three weeks ago.
>> You were married three weeks ago.
>> A
[applause]
>> Where'd you guys get married?
>> And Diamond Bar.
>> In Diamond Bar, the home of weddings.
>> How'd you ask her to marry you, sir?
>> At a steak, please.
>> Ma'am, can he talk?
It's only been three weeks, but he'd
like to say things, too.
Poor guy. just sat there quietly while
you answered all the questions.
>> Hello. Am I still here?
Unlike your her father, you're not
blessed. You're just sitting there. Shut
the [\h__\h] up, David. We're going to a
comedy show.
>> How did you ask me to marry us?
>> Uh, it take place in San Diego.
>> Take place in San Diego. What was it
called? San Diego Sticks. [laughter]
>> I don't know.
>> You don't know what it was called? Are
you okay?
It's only been a couple weeks. How can
you not remember the restaurant that you
got all liquored up and came out with a
wife at?
These steaks are fantastic. Want to get
married? Holy, it's happening.
Just a lady from Ecuador sitting on the
side eating fillets and waiting for her
sugar pap.
What's the age difference? What's the
age difference?
>> Five years.
>> Five years. Well, one of you is aging
much differently than [laughter]
being a dick.
>> One of you needs to get out of the sun.
[laughter]
>> Sorry, buddy. [laughter]
Thought you're a little older. Ma'am,
you're aging great.
>> What's What's your What's your beauty
regiment? How many times do you shower a
week?
>> I drink a lot of water.
>> You drink a lot of water, but how many
times do you shower a week?
>> What's that? Every day.
>> Every day. Ever do it twice in one day?
>> No. I knew it. I knew she didn't need to
There's a There's a water shortage. Quit
using all the water. Just go from the
sandwich place right to the gym. It
smells the same.
Sit down, officer.
[laughter] Some guy married a lady from
Ecuador. Ice came into the building out
of blue. [laughter]
That mustache gave you away, son.
Hat and a massive mustache.
I smell a crime out there. [laughter]
Are you a police officer?
>> No. Fireman?
>> Negative.
>> Negative. My god. Gave us his AIDS test
results.
>> Weird humble brag. Are you a fireman?
>> I'm negative. What do you think you do?
Why do you look like that? [laughter]
>> That guy's not a principal of a high
school. I'll tell you that much.
[laughter]
>> What do you do?
>> I work for customs. You work for
customs?
[applause]
>> Son of a [\h__\h] You've just taken my
crowd down by 50%.
84% of the Mexicans in here are paying
their bill right now because of you,
mother.
And she's legal now. She married that
guy 3 weeks ago.
You're free, ma'am. You're free to run.
Guy works for customs.
Terrifying mustache for customs.
By the way, just to let you know, one
two tables over the front [laughter]
pocket.
>> [laughter]
>> If you want to find him, just find an
old man working. Ask where his son is.
Him right there. He's probably out with
that guy riding motorbikes around.
>> Gasoline. Gasoline. Gasoline.
Gasoline.
Single. Wait, what? Are you Oh, that's
your wife right there. Fantastic.
Ma'am, how'd you meet Johnny Mustache?
[laughter]
Let me guess what shirt he was [snorts]
wearing when you met him. Mustache rides
freak.
You're like, "Oh my god,
>> I love the ride of faith." [laughter]
>> He says, "Not tonight." He's got his hat
turned around.
That mustache is closed for business.
[laughter]
How'd you meet him, ma'am? Tell us.
Everybody wants to know. People over
there curious. That lady just picked up
her phone. Those people are talking.
Mexicans are still nervous. [laughter]
>> High school.
>> High school. Oh my god. Where where you
guys you guys are in high school? Grade
12, just like those people.
>> We didn't start dating until after
college.
>> After college. Huh. So you met him like
in high school.
>> Then you went off to college and then
you were coming home probably from a
vacation someplace and he was working at
the customs.
>> [laughter]
>> And you're like, Steven Baldwin, is that
you?
Didn't recognize you with that massive
piece of fur.
[laughter]
Grown up a lot. Samantha
country's in my hands now. [laughter]
Making sure people are bringing back the
right amount of cigarettes they should
bring back. Okay.
[laughter]
>> What are you doing later on? You want to
go out and get me get a drink?
>> [laughter]
>> Did you hit on him or did he hit on you?
>> He hit on you. What did he say to you?
How did he say that?
>> I'm circumcised.
>> I know you see my mustache and probably
think I got a fliddly flop, but I don't.
[laughter]
>> What did he say? Is he circumcised
or is he running around with a covered
wagon? He's not circumcised.
>> Oh my god.
That's a sign of a smuggler right there.
Got half a pound of cocaine hidden under
his lap right there.
[laughter]
Nothing to declare.
Just haven't been caught. Got got hit by
a stingray on vacation.
>> Good for you. What did you what what was
your face when you found out it was
uncircumcised?
>> Promised my mom I'd never do this.
[laughter]
>> You're young. You probably don't know
what we're talking about.
The uncircumcised penis is terrifying.
Anyways, ma'am, tell us about the first
time you seen it. [laughter]
>> Were you shocked and surprised?
>> Tell us. Tell us. Everybody wants to
know. We're all sitting around this 24
year old. She She's on pins and needles
waiting to hear about this. She's in
love with a lady that comes to her gym.
Tell her.
>> Ma'am, have you seen an uncircumcised?
>> No.
>> Customs, come over.
Welcome her to America. [laughter]